中文字幕 by @aphan79
你跟警长说过你正走去内布拉斯加？
You told the sheriff that you were walking to Nebraska?
对
That's right.
说给我们听听
Tell me the story of us.
为什么我们在这
Why are we here?
你的生命不可思议
Your life is magic.
你开除我？
You're firing me?
这是个开除的机会
It's a fire-tunity.
那你要做什么
So what're you gonna do?
我要做我一直做的
I'm gonna do what I always do.
你这样会对不少人造成不少伤害
You're about to do a lot of damage to a lot of people.
我只是在思考怎么我在你身上浪费了两年半时间
I just keep thinking about how I wasted two and a half years on you.
为什么你不进来跟我说个战争的故事
Why don't you come on in here and tell me a war story.
电影是每秒24次的事实
你喜欢电影？
You like movies?
对我来说这是一部电影...
To me it's a movie...
...就像其他电影那样...
...like any other movie...
...只不过它里边有那么多好事儿
...only it has so many better things in it.
回家吧
Come home.
如果我们今天第一次在火车上相遇...
If we were meeting for the first time today on a train...
...你会让我跟你一起下车吗？
...would you ask me to get off the train with you?
从1到10来算 你觉得你是多少
On a scale of one to ten, what do you think you are?
A six.
我觉得你是3
I think you're a three.
我觉得你欠打
I think you need a shot.
那是我的路线
That's my line.
我不聪明 但是我会努力
I have no wisdom, but I will try my best.
我生命中所有的好都是因为有你
Everything good in my life is because of you.
想不想出去走走？我们走吧
You wanna get out of here? We'll get out of here.
我们去流浪
We'll hit the road.
中尉似乎发现自己在一颗还没爆的地雷上
Lieutenant here seems to have found himself on top of an unexploded mine.
我都不知道你的名字
I don't even know your name.
这是一起经典的诱拐
It's a classic kidnapping.
他们带走了我们的孩子还有罐头还有意大利面
They took our children and the canned goods and pasta.
来燃起心中的火
Here's to fire in our hearts.
它叫大脑冻结 你得小口喝
It's called a brain freeze, you need to learn to sip.
什么时候所有人都跟着沃尔特迪斯尼去迪斯尼乐园啦？
When does anybody get to go to Disneyland with Walt Disney himself?
我想给你看点东西
I wanna show you something.
假的
It's a fake.
你说什么？ 这不可能
What're you talking about? That's impossible.
人们相信他们愿意相信的
People believe what they wanna believe.
因为这家伙做的这么好 对所有人这就是真货
Cause the guy who made this was so good, that it's real to everybody.
现在谁是大师 画家还是造假的？
Now who's the master, the painter or the forger?
谁不喜欢一个好的魔术？
Who doesn't love a good magic trick?
绝对没有
Absolutely not.
我选你 因为我拥有你
I chose you, because I own you.
有时一个人必须选一边
Sometimes a man has to pick a side.
然后你会好好选
Then you should pick wisely.
有些战争你会奋战 有些你会走开
There are some wars you fight, and some wars you walk away from.
这是战斗类型
This is the fighting kind.
做了你就无路可退
You do this there's no going back.
你死得要有意义
Well you gotta die of somethin'.
欢迎来到达拉斯买家俱乐部
Welcome to the Dallas Buyers Club.
给他们看些精彩的老式美国自大
Let's show them some good old-fashioned American swagger.
娘的 你不错
Damn, you're good!
我们更上了一层楼...
We raised the bar...
...如果我们想呆在那...
...and if we wanna stay there...
...我们得冒着所有危险
...we gotta risk everything.
时间到
Time's up.
不管你认为你可能知道什么...
No matter what you think you might know...
...我们都会永远领先你一步 七步...
...we will always be one step, seven steps ahead of you...
...当你认为你追上来时...
...and just when you think you're catching up...
...那时我们将在你身后
...that's when we'll be right behind you.
想战斗？
Wanna fight?
2500吨的棒极了
Two thousand five hundred tons of awesome.
你是找麻烦或者麻烦总来找你？
You go looking for trouble or does it always find you?
我依旧问自己这个同样的问题
I still ask myself the same question.
好消息 车没坏
That's great news, car's fine,
更重要的是―
what's more important is-
我拿到下一张失业支票的时候...
When I get my next unemployment cheque...
...我要弄些Phil Wood极品花鼓 金轮胎 金链条
...I wanna get some Phil Wood hubs, gold tires, gold chain.
那是个专业啤酒品尝技能
That's an expert beer tasting technique.
啥？！
What?!
我不能 我不 我不能
I can't, I ca- I can't.
能不能请某人再狠狠打你的脸
Would somebody just please punch me in the face again?
我感觉像是她捡起了我刚放下的
I feel like she's picking up what I'm putting down.
但是然后她又放下了
But then again she's putting it down again.
但是然后她又捡起来了
But then she picks it back up.
老天
Jesus.
跟你的老板来杯啤酒
Having a beer with your boss.
你想跟我一起喝杯冰的 你让我知道
You wanna grab a cold one with me, you let me know.
不
No.
出局！
That's a out!
什么 我甚至都没有机会去-
What, I didn't even get a chance to-
是吗？
That's it?
拿到没？
Did you get it?
你现在是认真的？
Are you serious right now?
显然我要彻底好好再想想
Obviously I should have thought this through more.
这些不是你在找的机器人
These are not the droids you're looking for.
我爱那个 它是那么随机
I just love that, it's so random.
我中箭了！
I'm hit!
野蛮人
Savages.
真可怕
This is awesome.
我感觉你在呼吸氦气 我在呼吸氧气
I feel like you're breathing helium and I'm breathing oxygen.
是什么让你说出那个？
What makes you say that?
你会躺在这儿把头伸进门里吗？
Will you lay down here and put your head in the door?
然后我要使劲关门150，000次
Then I'll slam it about a hundred and fifty-thousand times.
我去找些该死的水 吃掉我所有那些该死的药片...
I'm gonna go find some damn water and take all my damn pills...
...然后我们开始这个派对
...then we're gonna get this party started.
喔喔喔，我喜欢！
Oooh, I like that!
那我们还等什么？
So what're we waiting for?
嘿老爸 是我
Hey dad, it's me.
不 一切都很好
No, everything's fine.
砰 砰 你死了！
Bang, bang, you're dead!
啪 啪 啪！
Pow, pow, pow!
你知道 我真的才开始理解像是为什么人们不再用这些了
You know, I'm really starting to understand like why people don't use these anymore.
嗯 它只是没意义
Yeah, it just doesn't make sense.
去顶上
Up top.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
如果你觉得我的人生很如意 你错了
If you think my life is just so easy, you're wrong.
那房间里似乎有个活的什么东西？
What's it like to be alive in that room right now?
你知道这个地方？
Do you know this place?
你以前看过任何人做这样的事吗？
Have you ever seen anybody do anything like this before?
这儿没有政治 这只是不错的老式复仇
There's no politics here, it's just good old-fashioned revenge.
我不想当一个好人...
I don't wanna be a good man...
...我要做一个伟人
...I wanna be a great one.
我不相信我们的命运没有其他选择
I don't believe that we have one fate and no choice.
我们塑造我们拥有的生活
We make our own lives.
那就是为什么你在这儿
That is why you are here.
我活下来了！
I survive!
我绝不会陷入绝望！
I will not fall into despair!
我会让自己强壮 直到自由的时刻
I will keep myself hardy 'till freedom is opportune!
我们今晚要让它通过...
We're gonna make it through tonight...
...一切都会没问题
...and everything is gonna be okay.
你是一个罪犯...
You are a criminal...
...我看到你谋杀了无辜的男女...
...I watched you murder innocent men and women...
...我奉命来终结你！
...I was authorized to end you!
我不能等待生活把你撕成碎片
I can't wait to watch life tear you apart.
它已找到你
It has found you.
这是唯一的出路
This is the only way.
你真相信神会下来拯救你吗？
You really believe that God will come down and save you?
跟他说下来阻止我
Tell him to come down and stop me.
你没法重复过去
You can't repeat the past.
不能重复过去？
Can't repeat the past?
不能
No.
为什么 你当然可以的
Why of course you can.